{"questions_list":[
		{
					"question": "1 score for every right answer. Welcome to Building B! Do you know this is the only building that has unique running hours. Enter the number of hours this Building runs",
					"hint": "Entrance door to this building may help you answer this. There is also a rumour that this building runs all day'.",
					"answer": "24"
				},
		{
					"question": "Great guess! What is the first thing you see on your left when you enter the building?",
					"hint": "Helps people move from floor to floor.",
					"answer": "Elevator"
				},
		{
					"question": "That was as easy as a piece of a cake! Now head straight and you will find 2 ways either left or right. How many labs and lecture theatre are there on this floor in total",
					"hint": "Watch out there are many doors here and some of them are neither a lab or a theatre. 'Look what the door says'.",
					"answer": "10"
				},
		{
					"question": "Perfect! Roam around this floor and look for 'staff only' door. Enter the number of this room accurately",
					"hint": "It is a 'unique colour' door.",
					"answer": "B2.26"
				},
		{
					"question": "Well done! Let's take stairs upto Level 3. The structure of all levels in this building are the same. Now that you are on level 3 look for door which says 'cleaners store'. Can you tell me the number of this room accurately?",
					"hint": "This is the only cleaners store in the entire building and is on level 3. ",
					"answer": "B3.11.01"
				},
		{
					"question": "Smart! Go back to the stairs and head straight. Look for personal lockers for students and staff. Can you count and enter the number of lockers in total?",
					"hint": "As you took stairs to level 3 and entered this floor. Go back to the exact spot and take a right. Easy to find the loakers",
					"answer": "60"
				},
		{
					"question": "Well done! What is the number of the last locker? Enter the number",
					"hint": "Wondering which is the last locker? Bottom last locker on your right hand side'.",
					"answer": "200"
				},		
		{
					"question": "I knew you would do it. Great! Walk down straight from the lockers to find printing machine. What is the first sentence under 'printer instructions'.",
					"hint": "Answer consists of only 5 words.",
					"answer": "swipe your card to login"
				},		
		{
					"question": "Spot on! Walk the opposite side to printers to cross lockers. Look for a room full of MACS 'MAC LAB'. Enter the number of MACS you see in this lab",
					"hint": "This is the only MAC lab on this floor.",
					"answer": "27"
				},		
		{
					"question": "Awesome! Let's go back to the stairs and climb to level 4. This is not a complicated floor so I won't direct you here. Look for the lecture theatre which says 'Bachelor of Nursing' only. What is the number of this theatre.",
					"hint": "Look for 'Bachelors of Nursing'. '1 digit answer'",
					"answer": "6"
				},		
		{
					"question": "Great mind! Just around Bachelor of Nursing theatre there is a lab and it has a computer with a unique 'DPN number' sticker on one the monitors. Find the computer and fill in the missing digit 'DPN4_705'",
					"hint": "Like I said in the question 'it is a digit'.",
					"answer": "0"
				},
		{
					"question": "Well done, You are just one answer away to finish this stage! Let me test your observation when you made your way upto level 4. Find a piece of art hanging on the wall and name the artist",
					"hint": "Read the question again 'when you made your way upto level 4'.",
					"answer": "Noela Stratford"
				}		
	]
}
